Guide to the Robert S. Rankin Papers, 1898 - 1977 (bulk 1927 - 1976) UA.29.02.0078
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Robert S. Rankin Department of Political Science Records, circa 1927-1977
  - Miscellaneous Folders, 1938-1968
    - Scrapbook Material, 1939-1968 (Box 10)
    - Committee on Faculty Organization and Academic Council, 1961-1962 (Box 10)
    - Newspaper Clipping: Quotation by Chief Justice Earl Warren, 1954 Feb. 15 (Box 10)
    - How to Pass Exams (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - Inactive Correspondence, 1930-1948 (Box 11)
    - Correspondence with Professor Edward S. Corwin (Princeton), John T. Caldwell, and Frances DeLancy, 1930-1936 (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 11)
    - Southern Political Science Association: Correspondence between R.S.R. and Professor Cullen B. Gosnell, 1930 Oct.-1936 Sept. (Box 11)
    - Southern Political Science Association and Political Science in the South, 1938 (Box 11)
    - Political Science Joint Program American Political Science Association Meeting, 1931 (Box 11)
    - American Political Science Association, 1933 (Box 11)
    - Political Science Department Catalogue, 1935 (Box 11)
    - Journal of Politics miscellaneous information, 1945-1949 (Box 11)
    - Journal of Politics Book Review Correspondence, 1944 (Box 11)
    - Journal of Politics Book Review Correspondence, 1943 (Box 11)
    - Journal of Politics Book Review Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - Overdue Reviews, circa 1944 Feb. (Box 11)
    - Book Review Letter sent to several South American recipients (Box 11)
    - Reviewers, Mechanics, etc., circa 1941-1942 (Box 11)
    - Books ordered from the publisher and general correspondence with publishers (Box 11)
    - Book Review, 1944 Feb. (Box 11)
    - Book Review, 1943 Nov. (Box 11)
    - Book Review, 1943 May (Box 11)
    - Book Review, 1943 Feb. (Box 11)
    - Book Review Material, 1942 Nov. (Box 11)
    - Book Reviews mailed 1942 Jun. 4 to Harris, 1942 Aug. (Box 11)
    - Journal of Politics, Taylor Cole, 1941 (Box 11)
    - American Arbitration Association Certificate, 1944 (Box 11)
    - American Political Science Association (Box 11)
    - Aa-Ap Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 11)
    - Ap-Az Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 11)
    - Big Brothers Bible Class: First Presbyterian Church, Durham (Box 11)
    - Ba-Bl Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 11)
    - Bm-Bz Correspondence, 1935; 1937-1948 (Box 11)
    - Ca-Co Correspondence, 1939-1948 (Box 11)
    - Co-Cz Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 11)
    - Conference on Current Inter-Governmental Problems (held at Duke), 1934 May 11-12 (Box 11)
    - Confidential Guide to Courses, Duke'n'Duchess, 1942 (Box 11)
    - Corwin, Edward S., Reprint of article from the American Bar Association Journal, 1939 Oct. (Box 11)
    - D Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 11)
    - Entertainments Series, 1929 and 1931 (Box 11)
    - E Correspondence, 1938-1948 (Box 11)
    - Faculty Committee on Athletics, 1936 (Box 11)
    - F Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 11)
    - Gibson, Professor William, 1944-1946 (Box 11)
    - G Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 11)
    - Hodges, Wiley E., 1937-1947 (Box 12)
    - Ha-Hl Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 12)
    - Hm-Hz Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 12)
    - I Correspondence, 1943-1948 (Box 12)
    - J Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 12)
    - Lectures, 1937-1940 (Box 12)
    - University Lecture Series (Alan K. Manchester), 1940 (Box 12)
    - Public Lectures, 1940-1941 (Box 12)
    - Lectures, 1940-1943 (Box 12)
    - Lectures, 1943-1944 (Box 12)
    - Lectures, 1945-1948 (Box 12)
    - La-Loc Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 12)
    - Lod-Lz Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 12)
    - Mc Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 12)
    - Ma-Me Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 12)
    - Mi-Mz Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 12)
    - Model State Constitution and Bill of Rights, St. Louis, 1941 (Box 12)
    - Fourth Edition of Model State Constitution, 1940 (Box 12)
    - N Correspondence, 1939-1948 (Box 12)
    - O Correspondence, 1938-1948 (Box 12)
    - O.P.A., 1944 (Box 12)
    - Political Science Tests and Outlines, 1943-1944 (Box 12)
    - Positions Offered and Letters of Recommendation, 1946-1948 (Box 12)
    - Princeton University Bicentennial, 1946 Oct. 7-9 (Box 12)
    - P Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 12)
    - Rotary Club, 1946-1948 (Box 12)
    - Rankin, R. S.: Biographical Data, 1938 (Box 12)
    - Rankin, Thomas Samuel (Father of R.S.R.) (Box 12)
    - R Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 12)
    - Sa-Sm Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 12)
    - Sn-Sz Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 12)
    - Southern Political Science Association, 1941-1948 (Box 12)
    - T Correspondence, 1940-1946 (Box 12)
    - Willkie, Wendell: Liberal Arts Education in a World at War address, 1943 (Box 12)
    - W Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 12)
  - Inactive RSR and Departmental Correspondence and Subject Files, 1937-1959 (Box 13)
    - A Correspondence, 1948 Dec.-1949 Dec. (Box 13)
    - Athletic Council, 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - Bm-Bz Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - Ca-Cn Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Co-Cz Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Campbell Foundation (John Bulow, W. B. Stubbs), 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - Cole, Professor R. Taylor, 1939-1949 (Box 13)
    - Connecticut Report (Commission on State Government Organization), 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - State of Connecticut Military Survey (Box 13)
    - Connery, Professor Robert H., 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Deener, David. R., 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Dialismos, Sypros, 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Duke University National Council, 1949 (Box 13)
    - D Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 13)
    - E Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Edwards, Margaret, 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - Elliott, Don. R., 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - F Correspondence, 1949 (Box 13)
    - G Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 13)
    - German Students, 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - Gordon, Harold, 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Gough, Carolyne, 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Griffin, Ernest, 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - Graduate School Bulletin, 1950 (Box 13)
    - Graduate Material (Dr. Cole), 1947-1949 (Box 13)
    - Graduate Material (Dr. Wilson), 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Ha-Hl Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - Hm-Hz Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Hallowell, Professor John H., 1946-1948 (Box 13)
    - Harmon, John, 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Hathorn, Guy B., 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Horn, Herman L., 1945-1949 (Box 13)
    - Howell, John M. (Box 13)
    - Hughes, Mrs. Clyde (Virginia Wood), 1949 (Box 13)
    - I Correspondence, 1949 (Box 13)
    - J Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 13)
    - K Correspondence, 1938-1950 (Box 13)
    - Lectures Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - M Correspondence, 1950 (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1948-1949 (Box 13)
    - N Correspondence, 1949 (Box 13)
    - O Correspondence, 1949-1951 (Box 13)
    - Oglesby, Roscoe R., 1949 (Box 13)
    - P Correspondence, 1949 (Box 13)
    - Positions Offered and Letters of Recommendation, 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - R Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Readings in American Government, 1937-1940 (Box 13)
    - Sn-Sz Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Seyler, William, 1949-1951 (Box 13)
    - Spearman, Eloise Lenore, 1949 (Box 13)
    - Spence, Professor H. E.: The Christmas Mummers (Box 13)
    - T Correspondence, 1937-1949 (Box 13)
    - Torch Club, 1946-1950 (Box 13)
    - Troutman, William F. Jr., 1946-1949 (Box 13)
    - V Correspondence, 1937-1950 (Box 13)
    - W Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Williams, John, 1948-1949 (Box 13)
    - Withrow, Stanton, 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - Wood, Virginia (Box 13)
    - X-Y-Z Correspondence, 1942-1948 (Box 13)
    - Department of Political Science, 1951-1954 (Box 13)
    - Staff and Personnel, 1951-1955 (Box 13)
    - Information on Graduate Students and Studies, 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Graduate Material, 1951-1952 (Box 13)
    - Barnes, Wallace R., 1950 (Box 13)
    - Canon, Alfred Orville, 1948-1949 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence with Dean Robert, 1948-1950 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence relating to inquiry of summer programs offering graduate courses in Political Studies, 1951 (Box 13)
    - Political Science 22, 61, and 62, 1939-1949 (Box 13)
    - Political Science 209, 1938-1949 (Box 13)
    - Political Science 310 (Box 14)
    - Political Science 161-162, 1949 (Box 14)
    - Political Science 230, 290-291, 1937-1949 (Box 14)
    - New Courses, 1949-1950 (Box 14)
    - Political Science 21, 1947-1948 (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous Papers, circa 1950-1951 (Box 14)
    - Budget, 1954 (Box 14)
    - Curriculum, 1957-1958 (Box 14)
    - Curriculum, 1956-1957 (Box 14)
    - Curriculum to 1956, 1951-1955 (Box 14)
    - List of Learned Societies (Box 14)
    - Majors, 1952-1953 (Box 14)
    - News and Notes, 1953 (Box 14)
    - Political Science 61 (Box 14)
    - Political Science 62 (Box 14)
    - Grade Distribution (Box 14)
    - Political Science 241 (Box 14)
    - Reports on Department: Graduate Instruction Report, 1955 (Box 14)
    - Department of Political Science: Schedules, Statistics, Report, 1951-1959 (Box 14)
    - Department of Political Science, 1947-1951 (Box 14)
    - Political Science Department: Movies (Visual Education), 1948-1949 (Box 14)
    - Data on Films, 1949-1950 (Box 14)
    - Expenses for Films (Box 14)
  - Correspondence, 1932-1972 (Box 15)
    - A Correspondence, 1950-1966 (Box 15)
    - Air Force ROTC, 1953 (Box 15)
    - American Arbitration Association, 1956-1966 (Box 15)
    - American Arbitration Association: Weyerhaeuser Co., Plymouth, N.C. (Box 15)
    - American Arbitration Association (American Tobacco Co. vs. D.P.& O. Workers of America, Local No. 15), 1954 (Box 15)
    - American Arbitration Association (Appalachian Electric Power Co. vs. International Brotherhood of Electric Workers), 1954-1955 (Box 15)
    - American Arbitration Association (Fieldcrest Mills vs. Textile Workers Union), 1953-1954 (Box 15)
    - American Arbitration Association (Highland Cotton Mills vs. Textile Workers Union of America), 1956-1957 (Box 15)
    - American Arbitration Association (Hercules Powder Co. and United Gas, Coke & CWA, Local 495), 1952-1954 (Box 15)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1954-1955 (Box 15)
    - American Political Science Association, 1951-1964 (Box 15)
    - Correspondence with Appleton, Century, and Croft Publishing re Freedom & Emergency Powers in the Cold War (Box 15)
    - Ashford, Douglas E., 1963 (Box 15)
    - Athletic Council, 1951-1962 (Box 15)
    - Ball, Margaret, 1962-1964 (Box 15)
    - Beck, Carl, 1956-1963 (Box 15)
    - Bernd, Joseph L., 1954-1961 (Box 15)
    - Braibanti, Ralph, 1962-1964 (Box 15)
    - Bolner, James, 1962 (Box 15)
    - Brookes, Edgar H., 1961-1963 (Box 15)
    - Black, Martin L. (University Schedule Committee), 1951-1955 (Box 15)
    - Buck, Philip W., 1951-1962 (Box 15)
    - B Correspondence, 1951-1966 (Box 15)
    - C Correspondence, 1951-1966 (Box 15)
    - Canadian Study, 1957 (Box 15)
    - City Council, 1952-1957 (Box 15)
    - City Council, 1957-1960 (Box 15)
    - City-County Charter Commission, 1958-1960 (Box 15)
    - City-County Charter Commission Committee Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 15)
    - Proposed Charter for Consolidated Government of Charlotte and Mecklenburg County, 1971 (Box 16)
    - Proposed Consolidation of City and County Government by Durham Chamber of Commerce, 1932 (Box 16)
    - A Proposed Charter for a Consolidated Government for the City of Durham and Durham County (Second Discussion Draft), 1972 (Box 16)
    - A Safer Durham (Box 16)
    - Canon, Alfred, 1951-1967 (Box 16)
    - Carnegie Endowment, 1951-1952 (Box 16)
    - Center for Southern Studies, 1965-1966 (Box 16)
    - Colombia University, 1952-1953 (Box 16)
    - Committee on Academic Standards, 1954 (Box 16)
    - Community Chest, 1950-1951 (Box 16)
    - College Field Trips, 1951-1952 (Box 16)
    - Congratulatory Messages (on appointment to the Civil Rights Commission) (Box 16)
    - Cosmos Club, 1959-1965 (Box 16)
    - Thomas Y. Crowell CO., 1954-1955, 1965 (Box 16)
    - Dallmayr, Winfried R., 1960-1965 (Box 16)
    - Correspondence re Rights of Patients in Mental Hospitals (Box 16)
    - deVyver, Frank T., 1950-1960 (Box 16)
    - Doyle, Wilson E., 1950-1956 (Box 16)
    - Duke-Durham Committee Chamber of Commerce, 1963-1964 (Box 16)
    - Dukes, Charles A., 1950-1956 (Box 16)
    - Dulles, Eleanor Lansing, 1962-1965 (Box 16)
    - Brayman, Harold (Dupont Company), 1950-1954 (Box 16)
    - Duke, Angier Biddle (Box 16)
    - D Correspondence, 1950-1966 (Box 16)
    - E Correspondence, 1950-1966 (Box 16)
    - Edens, A. Hollis, 1950-1961 (Box 16)
    - Ellis, Leon, 1950-1960 (Box 16)
    - Evans, Marcus H. Jr., 1961-1962 (Box 16)
    - F Correspondence, 1950-1966 (Box 16)
    - Faculty Club, 1949-1950 (Box 16)
    - Faculty Club Christmas Party File (Box 16)
    - Far Eastern Professorship, 1952-1953 (Box 16)
    - Fundamentals of American National Government and Fundamentals of American Government: National, State, and Local, 1951-1959 (Box 16)
    - G Correspondence, 1950-1966 (Box 16)
    - Gervin, Spencer R., 1953-1960 (Box 16)
    - Gibbons, William C., 1957-1958 (Box 16)
    - Gillespie, John S., 1958-1960 (Box 16)
    - Gosnell, Cullen B., 1956-1963 (Box 16)
    - Governmental Affairs Institute, South Carolina Survey Study, 1954 (Box 16)
    - Model State Constitution (Preliminary Draft, Sixth Edition), 1961 (Box 16)
    - Graves, W. Brooke, 1950-1964 (Box 16)
    - Greene, Lee S., 1950-1961 (Box 16)
    - Greenlaw, Paul S., 1955-1956 (Box 16)
    - Griffin, Ernest Ray, 1954-1965 (Box 16)
    - Gross, Paul M., 1949-1959 (Box 16)
    - Duke University Guide to Independent Study: American Government, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Hagan, Charles B., 1962-1964 (Box 17)
    - Hanson, Earl T., 1950-1960 (Box 17)
    - Havens, Murray C., 1959-1961 (Box 17)
    - Harris, Joseph P., 1951-1960 (Box 17)
    - Hatcher, William H., 1951-1962 (Box 17)
    - Heidenheimer, Arnold J., 1963 (Box 17)
    - Highsaw, Robert B., 1951-1958 (Box 17)
    - Herring, H. J., 1951-1965 (Box 17)
    - Hodges, Wiley E., 1951-1964 (Box 17)
    - Holcombe, Arthur N., 1958-1959 (Box 17)
    - Horn, Herman L., 1950-1968 (Box 17)
    - Howard, J. Woodford, Jr., 1962-1964 (Box 17)
    - Howard, L. Vaughn, 1953-1954 (Box 17)
    - Howell, John, 1952-1953 (Box 17)
    - Huckabee, Ellen, 1951-1957 (Box 17)
    - Hughes, Virginia Wood (Mrs. Clyde), 1950-1956 (Box 17)
    - Huss, John D., 1959-1960 (Box 17)
    - H Correspondence, 1951-1959 (Box 17)
    - H Correspondence, 1959-1966 (Box 17)
    - I Correspondence, 1950-1965 (Box 17)
    - John Paul Jones, 1968 (Box 17)
    - Dennis William Johnson (Box 17)
    - Jordan, B. Everett (Box 17)
    - Joslyn, Harvey L., 1961-1965 (Box 17)
    - Jumper, Roy E., 1951-1957 (Box 17)
    - J Correspondence, 1950-1966 (Box 17)
    - Kefauver, Estes, 1951-1960 (Box 17)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1960 (Box 17)
    - W. K. Kellogg Foundation (Box 17)
    - Kenyon, Michael, 1954-1955 (Box 17)
    - Kernaghan, Kenneth, 1963-1966 (Box 17)
    - Kline, Earl O., 1955-1966 (Box 17)
    - Knepper, David. W., 1951-1960 (Box 17)
    - K Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 17)
    - Lecture Committee, 1949-1955 (Box 17)
    - Library Council, 1957-1963 (Box 17)
    - Lambert, W. C. B., 1955-1957 (Box 17)
    - Lancaster, Lane, 1953-1959 (Box 17)
    - Leavelle, Arnaud B., 1955-1956 (Box 17)
    - L Correspondence, 1949-1966 (Box 17)
    - McCall, Margaret, 1949-1966 (Box 17)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Co. Inc., 1951-1958 (Box 17)
    - McKay, R. A., 1953-1963 (Box 17)
    - Mc Correspondence, 1949-1966 (Box 17)
    - Maass, Arthur, 1952-1957 (Box 17)
    - Manchester, Alan K., 1949-1957 (Box 17)
    - Manley, Harry S., 1951-1955 (Box 17)
    - Martin, Roscoe C., 1937-1960 (Box 17)
    - Mason, A. T., 1951-1964 (Box 17)
    - Mastro, Julius J., 1961-1964 (Box 17)
    - Milbrath, Lester, 1956-1963 (Box 17)
    - Milbrath (Box 17)
    - Milnor, Andrew J., 1958-1962 (Box 17)
    - M Correspondence, 1949-1956 (Box 17)
    - M Correspondence, 1957-1966 (Box 17)
    - National Conference on Citizenship (Box 18)
    - National Conference on Government (Colorado Springs, Colorado), National Municipal League (Box 18)
    - Duke University National Council (Box 18)
    - National Municipal League, 1954-1961 (Box 18)
    - N.C. Finishing Company, Textile Workers Union Arbitration (Box 18)
    - Nelson, Dalmas H., 1959 (Box 18)
    - Noble, Lawrence, 1951-1968 (Box 18)
    - North Carolina Textbook, 1949-1956 (Box 18)
    - N Correspondence, 1950-1966 (Box 18)
    - Otis Green Foundation, 1951-1954 (Box 18)
    - O Correspondence, 1950-1965 (Box 18)
    - Patterson, Eugene, 1965-1966 (Box 18)
    - Peters, Frank A., 1948-1953 (Box 18)
    - Phi Beta Kappa general information, 1964 (Box 18)
    - Phi Beta Kappa preliminary visiting scholar, 1964 (Box 18)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Visiting Scholar, 1964 fall (Box 18)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Visiting Scholar, 1965 spring (Box 18)
    - Phi Kappa Psi, 1940, 1944-1956 (Box 18)
    - Phi Kappa Psi Florida State Colonization, 1958 (Box 18)
    - Phi Kappa Psi, 1957-1965 (Box 18)
    - Report on Physical Education, 1963 Mar. (Box 18)
    - Committee on Physical Education, 1962-1963 (Box 18)
    - Pilant, Denny, 1959-1966 (Box 18)
    - Popular Government: The Proposed Constitution of North Carolina, 1959 Feb. (Box 18)
    - Powell, B. E., 1949-1964 (Box 18)
    - Price, Douglas, 1956 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence relating to Political Behavior Specialists, 1955 (Box 18)
    - Pre-Legal Student and the Study of Political Science, circa 1955-1956 (Box 18)
    - Pre-Legal Symposium, 1948-1950 (Box 18)
    - Symposium: The Presidency in Transition, 1949 (Box 18)
    - P Correspondence, 1950-1968 (Box 18)
    - Q Correspondence, 1943-1960 (Box 18)
    - Rahim, Abdul (Egyptian Ambassador), 1952 (Box 18)
    - R.S.R. Biographical Data (Box 18)
    - Ray, Joseph, 1952 (Box 18)
    - Recommendations, 1950-1965 (Box 18)
    - Redford, Emmette, 1954-1959 (Box 18)
    - Ford Foundation Grant on Research in Public Affairs, 1960-1966 (Box 18)
    - Richards, C. H., 1950-1966 (Box 19)
    - Riddick, Floyd, 1950-1966 (Box 19)
    - Robert, Joe (Request for Admission to Cosmos Club), 1966 (Box 19)
    - Robson, C. B., 1952-1955 (Box 19)
    - Ronning, C. Neale, 1961-1962 (Box 19)
    - Rotary Club, 1949-1964 (Box 19)
    - Rouse, Robert, 1956-1960 (Box 19)
    - Royal Order of Dizzy Dozen, 1949-1958 (Box 19)
    - Russo, Joseph, 1950-1960 (Box 19)
    - R Correspondence, 1950-1968 (Box 19)
    - Scarrow, Howard A., 1949-1957 (Box 19)
    - Sedition (writings concerning the definition of), 1958-1962, 1964 (Box 19)
    - Seyler, William C., 1950-1965 (Box 19)
    - Shatzer, J. B. (Arbitration), 1948-1949, 1966 (Box 19)
    - Silvia-Brown Correspondence, 1949-1952 (Box 19)
    - Smith, Malcolm, 1959-1965 (Box 19)
    - South Carolina: Study of Federal Grants-in-Aid, 1954 (Box 19)
    - Southern Regional Education Board, 1954-1956 (Box 19)
    - Southern Political Science Association, 1945-1964 (Box 19)
    - Southwestern University, 1947-1950 (Box 19)
    - Stanford University, 1947-1949 (Box 19)
    - Steiner, Kurt, 1955 (Box 19)
    - Steward, Alva Ware, 1954-1965 (Box 19)
    - Stewart, Paul D., 1938-1963 (Box 19)
    - Stone, Clarence, 1958-1962 (Box 19)
    - Stone, Jerry B. (Award), 1961-1966 (Box 19)
    - Stout, Hiram M., 1961-1962 (Box 19)
    - Sturm, Albert, 1950-1965 (Box 19)
    - Sweet, David, 1955-1958 (Box 19)
    - S Correspondence, 1948-1955 (Box 19)
    - S Correspondence, 1955-1966 (Box 19)
    - Travis, Martin B., Jr., 1948-1963 (Box 19)
    - T Correspondence, 1950-1968 (Box 19)
    - Ulmer, Sidney Shirley, 1954-1963 (Box 19)
    - U Correspondence, 1938-1957 (Box 19)
    - Vann, Carl R., 1961-1962 (Box 19)
    - Virginia Honors Examination, 1966 (Box 19)
    - V Correspondence, 1950-1966 (Box 19)
    - Walker, Herman, 1962-1964 (Box 19)
    - Watkins, James T. IV, 1950-1964 (Box 19)
    - Webb, Wilfred, 1959-1960 (Box 19)
    - Westphalen, Ferdinand A., 1952-1953, 1955 (Box 19)
    - Wheare, K. C., 1951, 1954-1956 (Box 19)
    - When Civil Law Fails, 1939-1940, 1963 (Box 19)
    - Winter, A.B., 1950-1962 (Box 19)
    - W Correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 19)
    - W Correspondence, 1957-1966 (Box 19)
    - XYZ Correspondence, 1950-1966 (Box 19)
    - Zink, Harold, 1952-1954 (Box 19)
  - Post-Retirement Activities, 1973-1977 (Box 20)
    - Bicentennial Forums, 1976 (Box 20)
    - Durham Bicentennial Steering Committee, 1974-1977 (Box 20)
    - Bicentennial—Documentary Film on Dissent and American Revolution in North Carolina (Box 20)
    - Center for Study of Aging and Human Development, Institute for Retired Professionals, Adaptation Study (Box 20)
    - Richmond County Forum, 1974 Jan.-Mar. (Box 20)
    - Granville County Forum, 1975 (Box 20)
    - Johnston County Forum, 1973, folder 1 of 2 (Box 20)
    - Johnston County Forum, 1973, folder 2 of 2 (Box 20)
  - Tusculum College, 1932-1976 (Box 21)
    - Tusculum College, 1967-1976 (Box 21)
    - Tusculum College, miscellaneous (Box 21)
    - Tusculum College, Class of 1920 Fiftieth Reunion, 1970 (Box 21)
    - Rankin, R. C., 1950-1965 (Box 21)
    - Wiber, R. E., 1950-1955 (Box 21)
    - Dugger, John, 1950-1961 (Box 21)
    - Tusculum College, 1953-1966 (Box 21)
    - Tusculum College, 1950-1952 (Box 21)
    - Tusculum College, 1938-1949 (Box 21)
    - Tusculum College, including information on: Thomas S. Rankin, Class of 1920, Correspondence with Walter Gray, 1932-1934 (Box 21)
    - Tusculum College Endowment Campaign, 1939-1940 (Box 21)